Sebastian Actis

Buenos Aires, Argentina \cdot <u>linkedin.com/in/sebastianactis</u> \cdot <u>https://github.com/sebaactis</u> +54 9 1169229469 \cdot sebaactis@gmail.com

I am passionate about technology and software development. Always looking for new opportunities to grow and learn.

I have experience in the use of SQL and in the payment methods field for more than 6 years, looking to enter the development sector.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Global Processing

Operational Control Analyst

Buenos Aires, Argentina

July 2022–Present

- SQL for generating reports for internal area control and metrics
- Data analysis for incident resolution
- Control and improvement of internal processes of the sector
- Report for external clients based on business rules
- Creation of daily control processes to validate the operation of the corresponding processes

Cabal Cooperativa Limitada

Analista Funcional

Buenos Aires, Argentina

April 2018-July 2022

- Parameterization of clients and businesses in the TQ system.
- Survey and development of operational processes in the sector
- Programming of rules and fraud control for prevention
- SQL for transactional reports

EDUCATION

INSTITUTO SUPERIOR TECNOLÓGICO EMPRESARIAL ARGENTINO

Technician in software development

Buenos Aires, Argentina

2024 - In progress

CODERHOUSE

Full Stack Developer

Buenos Aires, Argentina 2022 - 2023

Buenos Aires, Argentina

In pause

UNIVERSIDAD DE BUENOS AIRES

Bachelor's degree in information systems

SKILLS

- Frontend: CSS, React, Next, Astro, Tailwind, Bootstrap
- Backend: Node, Express, SQL, MongoDB, Prisma, Entity Framework, Firebase
- Herramientas: Postman, Insomnia, Docker, Git, Github
- *General*: Javascript, Typescript, C#

LANGUAGES

- Spanish: Native
- English: Intermediate